podtech.net 2014-06-27

# Podtech.net Privacy Policy | Tech Talk and Tech Reviews

### Podtech Privacy Policy

_Effective May 7, 2007_

PodTech.net and PodTech Network, Inc. (collectively, “PodTech”) is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. While you can use many features of PodTech anonymously, you may be required to provide personal information in some instances to access certain features.

PodTech provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of www.podtech.net (this "Site"). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our [PodTech Terms of Use](http://www.podtech.net/home/terms-of-use).

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

### Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information from users are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, (together, the “Service”) and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

#### Personally Identifiable Information

When you post a response to content on the Site (“Comment”) or send a video by email (“Email”) we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This is information about you that when on its own, or in combination with other identifiers, can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name and email address. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Service and administer your inquiries. Your Comments are visible to all viewers of our Site.

We also collect other non-identifying information through your use of the PodTech Player (e.g. user activity, the pages of the site that you visit, time spent on these pages and other statistics) (“Non-Identifying Information”).

We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to provide the Service and administer your inquiries.

### Cookies

While PodTech does not use "cookies" to collect information, third party advertisers on the Site may place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the third party advertisers' websites or all the functionalities of their services.

### Submitting a Comment or Sending an Email Via PodTech.net

As part of the Service, you are able to post Comments on, and send Emails from, the Site. In order to post a Comment or send an Email, you are required to submit your name and email address. If you choose to post a Comment, the name given will published along with your comment on the Site, but the email address you have provided will not be made public. If you choose to send an Email, both your name and your email address will be provided to the recipient of the Email. The recipient’s email address will be used only for the purpose of sending the Email to the addressee and for no other purpose. Podtech does not sell or distribute your Email address or your recipients’ Email addresses for any commercial purpose.

### Phishing

We do not and will not, at any time, request your Social Security Number, taxpayer ID or other personal financial information in a non-secure or unsolicited email or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information**. We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information with, and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information to, third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

**Service Providers**. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**. PodTech cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal processes (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of PodTech or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

**Business Transfers**. PodTech may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. In the event that the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy and you object to such a transfer, it is incumbent upon you to notify Podtech of your request to opt out of any such transfer. See below for privacy contact information 

### Changing or Deleting Your Information

All those who provide Personal Information to us, including those who post Comments, may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your Comment will also be deleted. If you would like us to delete the record of your Comment in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation to retain the record. See below for privacy contact information.

### Security

PodTech is very concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted, electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

### International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, PodTech transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents i) your agreement to that transfer; ii) your agreement to be bound by the applicable privacy laws that Podtech is governed by; your agreement to be bound by the jurisidiction and venue provisions of Podtech’s Terms of Use.

### Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### Our Policy Toward Children

This Site is not directed to children under age 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under age 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at Privacy AT podtech DOT net. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at Privacy AT podtech DOT net or at:

20950A Warner Center Ln.  
Woodland hills,CA 91367  
Tel: 818-206-9273
